Masked Self-Helper—The Hero of Justice
Brought to you by: Ko-FI.me/OrangeFlash
Ah! Please save me!
I'm Masked Self-Helper—The Hero of Justice!
I was waiting for this!
Way to go!
Give the bad guys a beating!
Good!
Punch 'em all!
Justice prevails in the end after all.
Can you please pull out the Hero of Justice from your 4-D Pocket?
No, I can't. That's so lame...
Though, I wonder what's so lame about being a fan of  Hero of Justice?
Whenever I'm in a terrible crisis, he always arrives on time and saves me.
I really really want the Hero of Justice.
There must be a way to create The Hero of Justice.
Well, I'll think how to create the Hero of Justice, now...
Well, he's so hopeless!
He's so helpless!
Alright, I will stay up and think till the morning!
Oh no! I forgot to do my homework!
Then finish your homework quickly!
But it's already too late!
Well, you sure are so helpless. I'll help you out.
It's really hopeless. There's no time left!
I wish one more person could help me!
Masked Self-Helper—The Hero of Justice!
Masked Self-Helper?
Doraemon, thanks. You're so reliable.
But I didn't summon him!
Let's do homework. There's not much time left.
Nobita, it's time for the breakfast. Hurry up or you'll be late for school!
Finished!
Thanks, Masked Self-Helper for helping me to finish my homework
But just who are you and where are you from?
It's better not to ask.
Now you have to attend the school.
Thank you, Mr. Masked Self-Helper.
Whenever I'm in trouble, please come and save me!
And thus Masked Self-Helper came to my help.
NObita, aren't you just over watching the super hero shows?
But that's so strange!
I wonder how did he find out that you're in trouble?
Of course he did. He's the Hero of Justice, after all.
I'm full!
I'm off to school!
I feel like I've seen his costume, heard his voice somewhere before.
Mornin', Nobita-kun!
You seem to be full of energy today.
Shizuka-chan, actually the Hero of Justice came to my rescue.
The Hero of Justice?
Nobita, are you listening to my lecture?
You're so spacing out from morning, so go and stand outside your class!
I've the Masked Self-Helper to help me, he'll come to my rescue in no time!
Come in!
Oh, it's raining.
Have you brought your umbrella, Shizuka-chan?
Nope. What about you?
Actually, I have the Hero of Justice coming to my help!
Ah, the Masked Self-Helper is here!
Here's your umbrella.
Thanks for coming to my rescue.
Shizuka-chan, get inside!
'Kay.
Thank you, Masked Self-Helper!
But I forgot to bring my own umbrella!
Outside has been fully dried. It's playtime!
I have the the Masked Self-Helper—The Hero of Justice by my side!
He will come help me whenever I need him!
Oh, it's Giant!
Alright!
What's up, Nobita?
Not really!
Why are you following me?
For no reason.
You sure are creepy!
Oh, you're here now?
But there's no thrill now.
Giant has gone.
Can you please try to not invite trouble, deliberately?
I can't come to save you all time.
You call your self Hero of Justice? You'd better be responsible.
Okay?
Ah, Nobita-kun!
Why did you kick me?
I've got Masked Self-Helper by my side.
Wait... He's gone...!?
Not so fast, Nobita!
Stop!
How dare you kick me?
Wait!
Masked Self-Helper, please come and save me!
Freeze, Takeshi!
You're out on streets, being violent towards others again!
I'm taking you home with me!
Sorry, Mum!
Still, I wonder who the Masked Self-Helper really is...?
Nobita, do you want to keep the costume you wore in the play?
Show me!
Ah, this is...!
I've figured it all out. The Masked Self-Helper really were the future you, all along.
Say what?
So no wonder why he knows all the troubles you faced today!
That is correct...
The future you, self traveled through time to help yourself.
To help me?
Since you went to the past now, the past you was saved.
Oh, I did self-service?
The time has been ran out.
Masked Self-Helper, right at your service!